Vladimir	B-PERSON
Putin	I-PERSON
is	O
dead	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
shot	O
in	O
Moscow	B-GPE
.	O

Washington	B-GPE
DC	I-GPE
and	O
Washington	B-GPE
state	O
are	O
named	O
after	O
George	B-PERSON
Washington	I-PERSON

I	O
eat	O
and	O
apple	O
while	O
I	O
watch	O
a	O
movie	O
on	O
my	O
Apple	B-ORG
computer	O
.	O

I	O
live	O
in	O
Austria	B-GPE
but	O
Microsoft	B-ORG
wants	O
me	O
to	O
move	O
to	O
Germany	B-GPE
and	O
Google	B-ORG
wants	O
me	O
to	O
move	O
to	O
France	B-GPE
.	O

